<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="http://www.eclipse.org/projects/project-plan.xsl"?>
<plan plan-format="1.0" xmlns="http://www.eclipse.org/project/plan" xmlns:html="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"
      name="Project Name">
   <release projectid="technology.windowbuilder" version="1.5"/>
   <introduction>
     <html:div><html:p><html:b>WindowBuilder</html:b> is a powerful and easy to use bi-directional Java GUI designer that makes it very 
      easy to create Java GUI applications without spending a lot of time writing code to display simple forms. With
      <html:b>WindowBuilder</html:b> 
      you can create complicated windows in minutes.  Use the visual designer and Java code will be generated for you. You can easily 
      add controls using drag-and-drop, add event handlers to your controls, change various properties of controls using a property editor, 
      internationalize your app and much more.</html:p>
     </html:div>
   </introduction>
   <release_deliverables>
     <html:div><html:p>The WindowBuilder project delivers a bi-directional Java GUI designer that can be installed as a feature into an Eclipse IDE installation using an update site.</html:p></html:div>
   </release_deliverables>
   <release_milestones>
      <preamble />
      <milestone date="06/27/2012" milestone="1.5.0"><html:div>WB 1.5.0 should be released and included in the Juno simultaneous release</html:div></milestone>
      <milestone date="09/28/2012" milestone="1.5.1"><html:div>WB 1.5.1 should be released and included in the Juno SR1 release</html:div></milestone>
      <postamble />
   </release_milestones>
   <target_environments>
     <html:div>WindowBuilder requires Java 6 and runs on Eclipse 3.5 and greater.</html:div>
     <internationalization>
          <html:div><html:p>WindowBuilder is prepared to be translated. Translation relevant String constants are externalized into resource bundles.</html:p></html:div>
     </internationalization>
   </target_environments>
   <compatibility_with_previous_releases>
       <html:div>Binary and source compatibility is expected with the previous release.</html:div>
   </compatibility_with_previous_releases>
   <themes_and_priorities>
     <preamble>
         <html:div>We have the following major themes for our Juno release:</html:div>
     </preamble>
     <theme name="Ensure that WindowBuilder works fine with Eclipse 4.2">
        <description><html:p>As the Juno simultaneous release is going to be based on Eclipse 4.2, WindowBuilder needs to work properly when installed as a feature in an Eclipse 4.2 IDE.</html:p></description>
     </theme>
     <theme name="Add support for e4 development">
        <description><html:p>WindowBuilder needs to support creating and editing e4 ViewParts.</html:p></description>
     </theme>
     <theme name="Community support">
        <description><html:p>The WindowBuilder team needs to continue supporting users who wish to use WB to create their Swing and SWT user interfaces as well as developers wishing to use WB as a base for creating their own custom UI builders.</html:p></description>
     </theme>
   </themes_and_priorities>
   <!-- 
   <appendix name="Project Refactoring">
     ...html...
   </appendix>
    -->  
 </plan>
